TONI CATER

Designer | Illustrator



tonic.illustration@gmail.com



416-795-8213



Tonicater.me

About Me

I'm a designer who specializes in branding, editorial and digital design. I also specialize in editorial illustration and book design.

Skills

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe In Design
Adobe After Effects
Adobe Premiere
HTML5/CSS/Javascript

Hobbies

Painting watercolor portraits
I absolutely love to cook
A great baker.

Social Media

@Tonicaterdesigns ©

@tonicdesigns B

@Toni Cater in

Education

(BDES) Bachelors of Design, at the Ontario College of Art and Design.

2013 - 2018

Completed the OSSD Diploma and Regional Arts Certificate from Mayfield Secondary School.

2008 - 2012

Experience

Graphic Designer, Illustrator and Video Editor at Enable Education Training and Consulting

Sept 2018 - Present

Been credited with designing graphics for Women in View for their statistic and annual report. **2019**

Completed 4 month contract for LAMP. Completed their Annual Report for years **2018**, and **2019**.

Graphic Design Instructor for FEMMTO program at UforChange

Aug 2018- Sept 2019

Design and Communication
Coordinator for UforChange
May 2017- Present

Achievements

Started my own design business and have designed for a number of non for profits

2019- Present

Organized the Ontario College of Art and Design's BLXCK Association

2016 - Present

Student Moderator for panel discussion at the Black Speculative Arts Movement Event at the Ontario College of Art and Design

Sep 2016

Student Co-Organizer of Black Fractals and Black Future Month Celebrations at the Ontario College of Art and Design

Sep 2015 - May 2016

TONI CATER

Designer | Illustrator



tonic.illustration@gmail.com



416-795-8213



Tonicater.me

About Me

I'm a designer who specializes in branding, editorial and digital design. I also specialize in editorial illustration and book design.

Skills

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe In Design
UI/UX Design
Adobe After Effects

Hobbies

Painting watercolor portraits
I absolutely love to cook
A great baker.

Social Media

@Tonicaterdesigns @

@tonicdesigns B

@Toni Cater in

References

Melissa Bent

Head of HR at Enable Education

Perry Phalla

Program Coordinator

Geoff Snack

Digital Strategist and Brand Consultant/Shopify UX Program Specialist

Jonathan Gillett

Software Engineer, CTO of Investabit Melissa@enableeducation.com

Perry@uforchange.org

647-880-0860

geoffsnack@gmail.com

905-409-9190

jonathan.gillett@uoit.net